A Guide to the Thomas Inge papers, 1879-2001
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series I - Comic Arts
  - Sub-series D - Other Comic Related Items
    - Other:
      - Superman's Death News Clippings, undated, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
      - Calendars - wall, desk & personal 1976, 1979, 1980, 1983, 1989, 1990, 1992, 1993, 1996, 1998, 1999, 2000 (Box 46)
        1976: Official National Lampoon Bicentennial Calendar
        Science Fiction Calendar
        1979: Book of Days: Virginia Slims Engagement Calendar
        1980: Karehdayva Russian Calendar
        The Occult World of Doctor Strange Marvel Comics Calendar
        Wretched Mess Calendar
        1983: Graffiti Calendar
        1989: Hanna-Barbera 30th Birthday Calendar
        1990: Skip Marrow
        1992: The Neighborhood
        The Far Side 1992 Desk Calendar
        1993: The Far Side 1992-93 16-Month Wall Calendar
        The Far Side 1993 Desk Calendar
        The Ren & Stimpy Show
        1996: Looney Tunes
        1998: Prince Valiant: in the Days of King Arthur
        1999: 100 Years of American Comics
        2000: Drawn & Quarterly
      - Marvel: an Indexed Guide to Superhero Comics Issued through January 1975 (Box 47)
      - Marvel: Superhero Comics Index, Part One: The Amazing Spider-Man (Box 47)
      - The Spider-Man Reading Motivational Kit, 1975 (Box 48)
        Includes filmstrips, flash cards, cassettes, poster, and comic books.
      - Walt Disney: The Wide World of Energy Multimedia Kit, 1976 (Box 49)
        Includes filmstrip, cassette, game and pieces, posters, and comic books
    - Character Drinking Glasses
      - "Catching the Big One," Norman Rockwell Saturday Evening Post Covers, undated (Box 50)
      - Superman, 1975 (Box 50)
      - Sylvester & Tweetie Bird, 1976 (Box 50)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University Rams, undated (5 glasses) (Box 50)
      - Yosemite Sam, 1973 (Box 50)
      - Petunia Pig, 1973 (Box 50)
      - Slyvester & Tweetie, 1976 (Box 50)
      - Porky Pig & Taz, 1976 (Box 50)
      - Walt Disney's 100 Year's of Magic, 2002 (Box 50)
        "...it all started by a mouse"
        "...nature herself writes the most interesting stories"
        "Today we are shapers of the world of tomorrow."
        "Fantasy...lies beyond the reach of time"
      - Born Loser Coffee Mug, 1995 (Box 51)
      - Mickey Mouse milk glass coffee mug, undated (Box 51)
      - Road Runner & Wiley E. Coyote, 1976 (Box 51)
      - Petunia & Porky Pig, 1976 (Box 51)
      - Superman, 1975 (Box 51)
      - Beaky Buzzard, 1973 (Box 51)
      - Daffy Duck, 1973 (Box 51)
      - Leghorn Foghorn, 1976 (Box 51)
      - DC Superhero Party Cups, undated (Box 51)
      - Hardee's Marvel Comic Presents Spider-man & Captain American in "Doc on the Rocks," 1990 (Box 51)
      - Hardee's Marvel Comic Presents the Incredible Hulk & the Sensational She-Hulk in "The Green Team", undated (Box 51)
    - Buttons and other Miscellaneous Small Items
      - Alfred E. Newman, 1994 (Box 52)
      - Bloom County Fan Club of America, undated (Box 52)
      - Brotherhood of the Bronze, The, undated (Box 52)
      - Carl Barks Fan Club, undated (Box 52)
      - Cartoon Art Museum, undated (Box 52)
      - EC Fan-Addict Convention, 1972 (Box 52)
      - Eerie Magazine Fan Club, 1972 (Box 52)
      - Film Funsters, undated (Box 52)
      - F. O. M., The, undated (Box 52)
      - I Am Having Fun with Zippy, undated (Box 52)
      - I Go Pogo, 1979 (Box 52)
      - Infinity Gauntlet: the End is Here, The, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Krazy Kat, undated (Box 52)
      - Museum of Cartoon Art, undated (Box 52)
      - Pogo Fan Club Member, 1995 (Box 52)
      - Pogo Fan Club Member, 1996 (Box 52)
      - Snoopy Fan Club, undated (Box 52)
      - Spirit, The, 1982 (Box 52)
      - Steve Canyon Magazine, 1982 (Box 52)
      - Vote DC, 1995 (Box 52)
      - Vote Marvel Comics, undated (Box 52)
      - WAM, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Carl Barks Fan Club Pinched Penny, 2002 (Box 52)
      - Mickey: 60 Years with You, undated (Box 52)
      - Mickey's 60th Birthday 1928 - 1988, 1988 (Box 52)
      - Superman at 50, undated (Box 52)
      - The Closet of Comics/Dreaming City Comics, 1997 (Box 52)
      - Woodblock Stamp, undated (Box 52)
      - Woodblock Stamp, undated (Box 52)
      - Woodblock Stamp, undated (Box 52)
    - The Disney Decades Coins
      - #16 1926 - WD Studio Move to Hyperion (Box 53)
      - #28 1984 - Splash (Box 53)
      - #31 1935 - The Band Concert (Box 53)
      - #32 1940 - The Disney Studio moves to Burbank (Box 53)
      - #33 1950 - Cinderella (Box 53)
      - #34 1979 - The Black Hole (Box 53)
      - #36 1954 - 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea (Box 53)
      - #38 1973 - Robin Hood (Box 53)
      - #39 1994 - The Lion King (Box 53)
      - #41 1942 - Mickey's Birthday Party (Box 53)
      - #42 1951 - Alice in Wonderland (Box 53)
      - #43 1977 - Herbie Goes to Monte Carlo (Box 53)
      - #44 1988 - Who Framed Roger Rabbit (Box 53)
      - #45 2000 - Dinosaur (Box 53)
      - #46 1941 - Dumbo (Box 53)
      - #48 1962 - Minnie's Nieces, Millie & Melody (Box 53)
      - #50 1997 - Flubber (Box 53)
      - #51 1933 - Mickey Mouse Magazine (Box 53)
      - #52 1947 - Christmas on Bear Mountain (Box 53)
      - #54 1983 - Mickey's Christmas Carol (Box 53)
    - Shopping Bags & Gift Boxes:
      - Disneyland, undated (Box 54)
      - DC Comics, 1996 (Box 54)
      - Disney Store, The, undated (Mickey Mouse) (Box 54)
      - Disney Store, The, undated (Goofy) (Box 54)
      - Dupuis, undated (Box 54)
      - Mickey Mouse Gift Box, undated (Box 54)
      - Phil Seuling's Comic Art Convention, 1977 (Box 54)
      - Phil Seuling's Comic Book Marketplace, undated (Box 54)
      - Ringling Bros. & Barnum & Bailey Circus World, 1973 (Box 54)
      - Snoopy's Gallery & Gift Shop, undated (Box 54)
      - Warner Bros., 1993 (Box 54)
      - Walt Disney World, undated (Box 54)
      - Walt Disney World: Together at Disney, 1985 (Box 54)
    - Superman Sheet Set, 1979 (Box 55)
    - Tom & Jerry Wrapping Paper, undated (Box 55)
    - An American Salute to Entertainment, undated 1994 (Box 56)
      Includes two collector's books, first day cover stamps, and related paperwork
    - Brass Paper Weight, undated (Box 57)
    - Children's Facial Tissues featuring Disney Characters, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Commemorative Medallion - Batman, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Commemorative Medallion - Superman, 1988 (Box 57)
    - Commemorative Medallion - Wonder Woman, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Diamond International Galleries, Opening of the "Vault," 1995 (Box 57)
    - Donald Duck Orange Juice Carton, undated (Box 57)
    - G. I. Joe Official Trading Cards, unopened wax pack, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Looney Tunes Valentines for Children, undated (Box 57)
    - McDonald's 101 Dalmatians Snow Dome - Dalmatian Celebration, 1996 (Box 57)
    - McDonald's 101 Dalmatians Snow Dome - Dog Sledding, 1996 (Box 57)
    - McDonald's 101 Dalmatians Snow Dome - Snow Flurries, 1996 (Box 57)
    - McDonald's Hercules Plates - "Hold Your Horses Dinner's Coming!," 1999 (Box 57)
    - McDonald's Hercules Plates - "I'm a Meat & Potatoes Kind of Guy," 1999 (Box 57)
    - Mickey Magnetic Memo Clip, undated (Box 57)
    - Pinocchio 50th Anniversary 1940-1990 Christmas Ornament, 1990 (Box 57)
    - Politicards, 1980 (Box 57)
    - Rubber Stamps, undated (Box 57)
    - Rocketeer Trading Cards, unopened wax pack, undated (Box 57)
    - Snoopy Pez Dispenser, undated (Box 57)
    - Superman Three-piece Melamine Dinner Set, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Virginia Slims Book of Days Calendar, 1981 (Box 57)
    - Walt Disney Christmas Ornament, 1977 (Box 57)
    - Walt Disney Christmas Ornament, 1978 (Box 57)
    - Ziggy Valentines for You, undated (Box 57)
    - T-shirt featuring Calvin & Hobbes, undated (Box 58)
    - T-shirt featuring Superman, 1996 (Box 58)
    - Land's End Catalog, 1996 (Box 58)
    - T-shirt Mickey Mouse: Reading, it's an adventure, undated (Box 58)
    - Festival of Cartoon Art Tote Bag, 1995 (Box 58)
    - Broomhilda Doll, undated (Box 58)
    - Spiderman needlepoint pillow, 1978 (Box 58)
    - "A Night at the Opera" Keychain, undated (Box 59)
    - Batman 8 inch action figure, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Coca Cola Fifth Anniversary Reprint metal plaque, 1990 (Box 59)
    - Lex Luthor Notebook, 1975 (Box 59)
    - Mickey Mouse plague/wall hanging, undated (Box 59)
    - Royal Pavilion at Brighton Playing Cards, undated (Box 59)
    - Shazam! 8 inch action figure, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Superman 8 inch action figure, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Bart Simpson doll, 1990 (Box 60)
    - Bart Simpson plastic figure, 1990 (Box 60)
    - Felix the Cat plastic figure, 1989 (Box 60)
    - Lisa Simpson, 1990 (Box 60)
    - Mickey Mouse Fantasia plastic figurine, undated (Box 60)
    - Mickey Mouse Wall Clock, undated (Box 60)
    - Pink Panther plastic figure (missing head), undated (Box 60)
    - Pluto plastic figure, undated (Box 60)
    - Road Runner plastic figure (missing head), undated (Box 60)
    - Speedy Gonzales, 1968 (Box 60)
    - Sylvester the Putty Cat, plastic figure, 1969 (Box 60)
    - Superman plastic figurine, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Wiley E. Coyote plastic figure, 1968 (Box 60)
    - Unidentifiable ceramic figurine, undated (Box 60)
    - Unidentifiable wooden figure, undated (Box 60)
    - Blassie (Box 61)
      "No Bout About It" & "Blassie, King of Men" b/w "U.S. Male" & "Pencil Neck Geek"
    - Cotton Ivy (Box 61)
      100% Cotton
    - Good Tone Banjo Boys (R. Crumb): (Box 61)
      "Duck Yas Yas" b/w "Beautiful Missouri Waltz"
    - R. Crumb and his Keep-on-Truckin' Orchestra (Box 61)
      "Wisconsin Wiggles" b/w "River Blues"
    - Various Artists (Box 61)
      The Amazing Spider-Man & his Friends
    - Morning Funnies Cereal: 1st Collector's Edition, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Superman Peanut Butter, 1981 (Box 62)
    - Early American Literature - "The Legend of Sleepy Hollow" - lecturer M. Thomas Inge, 1976 (Box 63)
    - Ray & Bob Cassette, undated (Box 63)
    - Vaughn Bodé Program at Bowling Green State University 11.15.1972 (Box 63)
    - "What's So Funny about the Comics" Will Eisner, Art Speigelman, Tom Inge at New York Hilton 12.30.1978 (Box 63)
    - Untitled Cassettes (Box 63)
  - Sub-series E - Oversize
    - Altered Comic Strips, undated (Box 64)
    - Bark's Foundation Certificate, The, 1983 (Box 64)
    - Carl Barks Fan Club, 2001 (Box 64)
    - Comic Articles, 1933 (Box 64)
    - Comic Character Collage Poster, undated (Box 64)
    - Doonesbury Artwork, 1985 (Box 64)
    - English Teaching Seminar in Poznan, Poland, 1985 (Box 64)
    - Frank Frazetta Fantasy Illustrated Packet, 1997 (Box 64)
    - Hardee's Restaurant Tray Paper, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Hollywood Toy Television Program, undated (Box 64)
    - Humor Book Bibliography, undated (Box 64)
    - Mad Magazine, Cover Reprints, undated (Box 64)
    - Ministéro Da Educa翯, 1981-1983 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork, undated (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Comic Strips, 1980, 1987 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, undated, 1975, 1977-1979, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings - Comics 1 of 2, undated, 1971, 1974-1982, 1984 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings - Comics 2 of 2, undated, 1975-1978, 1980-1984, 1986, 1994 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Photocopied Articles, undated (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Posters, undated, 1974 (Box 64)
    - My Picture Autograph Album of Stage & Screen Stars, undated (Box 64)
    - Postage Stamps - Full Sheets, 1989-1990 (Box 64)
    - Prince Valiant, undated, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Shock SuspenStories Cover Art, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Shoe Artwork, 1988 (Box 64)
    - Supergirl Education Packet, 1985 (Box 64)
    - Tales from the Crypt Cover Art, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Trumbo, Phil, undated (Box 64)
    - Truth Funnies, undated (Box 64)
    - Two-Fisted Tales Cover Art, 1980 (Box 64)
    - Vault of Horror Cover Art, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Walt Disney's Uncle Scrooge Poster, 1994 (Box 64)
    - Weird Fantasy Cover Art, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Weird Science Cover Art, 1981 (Box 64)
    - American Humor: an Interdisciplinary Newsletter, Pen & Ink Header, undated (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Cartoonist Exchange Laugh Finder, 1943 (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Lone Ranger Comic Strip Reprint, undated (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Sketches, undated, 1952 (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Vaughn F. Bode Print, 1971 (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Yellow Jacket Editor Mock Up, 1958 (Box 65 - oversized)
    - Folder 1 Walt Disney Posters (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 2 Disney Characters, Popeye Adult Posters, Snoopy Come Home (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 3 Drawings, Sketches, Self Portrait by Inge (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 4 General Cartoon Posters (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 5 Famous Authors Posters, Literary, Terry Carroll Pen & Ink prints (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 6 Antique Movie, Circus, Entertainment Posters, VMFA - Andy Warhol (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 7 Superheroes Posters (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 8 Science Fiction Posters (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 9 New York World, Cartoon Page, 1903; The Witchita Daily Eagle, 1906 (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 10A Photocopies of Barney Google (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 11 Gilbert Shelton Comic Proofs (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 12 Topeka Daily Comic Strip Page, Sunday, August 19, 1934 (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 13 Krazy Kat Poster Board (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 14 Tundra Comic Promotional Poster (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 15 Charles Atlas Physical Culture (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 16 Fantasy Art Prints - Various Artists (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 17 Words & Picture Museum Promotional Prints - Various Artists/Subjects (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 18 Music/Band Promotional Poster (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 19 Superman Posters, Cut Out, Funeral for a Friend related items (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 20 San Francisco Examiner Comic Strip Page, 1916 (Box Map Case Drawer 84)
    - Folder 21 Old Comic Photograph Proofs (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 22 Maps of the Land of Oz (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 23 Krazy Kat strips - Original, 1922; Photocopies 1920 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 24 Dupont Circle Comic Strip Samples (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 25 The World Comic Page, 1894 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 26 Walter Blair Artwork (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 27 International Cartoon Festival of Budapest, Budapest City Maps (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 28 King Feature Promotional Packets (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 29 Brazilian Comic Strips: A Gazeta, Vitoria, Espirito Santo, May, 2000 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 30 Eerie Board Game, Newspaper Reproduction (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 31 Fritz the Cat 24C Animation Cell (found with Inge's collection in an envelope addressed to Jerry Muller) (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 32 Literary Posters, undated, 1986 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 33 Art Exhibition Posters, 1987, 1995 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 34 Editorial Cartoonist, 1991 (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
    - Folder 35 Miscellaneous Art Prints, undated (Box Map Case Drawer 85)
- Series II - Other Literary Materials and Personal Items
  - Sub-series: A - Ellen Glasgow
    - Frontier Humor, with corrections and editing notes, 1971, 1 of 3 (Box 66)
    - Frontier Humor, with corrections and editing notes, 1971, 2 of 3 (Box 66)
    - Frontier Humor, with corrections and editing notes, 1971, 3 of 3 (Box 66)
    - Ellen Glasgow: Centennial Essays, galley proofs, 1975 (Box 66)
    - Ellen Glasgow: Centennial Essays, with corrections and editing notes, 1976, 1 of 3 (Box 67)
    - Ellen Glasgow: Centennial Essays, with corrections and editing notes, 1976, 2 of 3 (Box 67)
    - Ellen Glasgow: Centennial Essays, with corrections and editing notes, 1976, 3 of 3 (Box 67)
    - Editorial matters, undated, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Rubin, undated, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Jones: Northern Exposure, undated, 1974 (Box 67)
    - MacDonald: Glasgow, Cabell and Richmond, undated (Box 67)
    - Scura: Glasgow and the Southern Renaissance: the Conference at Charlottesville, undated, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Jones: The Earliest novels, undated, 1975 (Box 67)
    - McDowell: Humorist, Mannerist, Psychologist, Ironist, and Artist: Ellen Glasgow in her Prewar Novels, undated, 1973 (Box 67)
    - Holman, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Rouse: Ellen Glasgow's Civilized Men, undated, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Parent Frazee: Ellen Glasgow, a Feminist?, undated (Box 67)
    - Inge: Introduction: Mississippi Quarterly, 1974 (Box 67)
    - MacDonald: Mississippi Quarterly, undated (Box 67)
    - Scura: Mississippi Quarterly, undated (Box 67)
    - Mississippi Quarterly, The, 1974 (Box 67)
  - Subseries B - Personal Items
    - Artwork:
      - Self Portraits, undated (Box 68)
      - Newspaper Comic Strip, 1915 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Personal Artwork, undated, 1950, 1951 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Published Artwork, undated, 1954 - 1956 (Box 68)
    - Other:
      - American History through Comic Art, undated (Box 68)
      - American Humor: an Interdisciplinary Newsletter Membership & Subscription Blank, undated (Box 68)
      - American Literature Section/Modern Language Association, 1981, 1982 (Box 68)
      - American Studies Association Newsletter, 1984 (Box 68)
      - Annie: A Theater Memoir, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Archives of American Art, 1975 (Box 68)
      - Author's Intention: an Exhibition for the Center for Editors for American Authors, 1972 (Box 68)
      - California State University Summer Arts, 1990 (Box 68)
      - City of Oslo Art Collectors, The, undated (Box 68)
      - Clemson University, 1982 - 1984 (Box 68)
      - Commonwealth Times, 1970 (Box 68)
      - Confederation of Virginia Arts Organization, 1978 (Box 68)
      - English Composition Text with Essay, The, 1978 (Box 68)
      - English 374: American Literature, Early 20th Century, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Faulkner & Yoknapatawpha Conference, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Great People & Great Ideas for Teaching English, 1978 (Box 68)
      - Hemingway Newsletter, The, 1984 (Box 68)
      - Histomap of Religion, undated (Box 68)
      - Historic Richmond Foundation Bumper Sticker, undated (Box 68)
      - Immoral Majority, undated (Box 68)
      - Institute for the Study of Universal History through Arts and Artifacts, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Kappa Tau Zeta of Lamba Chi Alpha Fraternity at Randolph Macon College, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Legacy: A Newsletter of Nineteenth Century American Women Writers, 1984 (Box 68)
      - Lamar House Bijou Theater, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Lawrence Scripps Wilkinson Foundation Collection of Famous Trains, 2000 (Box 68)
      - Levi Strauss & Co.: The American Hero: Myths & Media" Conference, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1977-1979 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Brochure, undated, 1978, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Business Cards, undated (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Certificates, undated, 1955, 1956, 1982 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1976, 1981, 1985, 1995 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Program Books, undated, 1977, 1983, 1987, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Mississippi History, 1987 (Box 68)
      - Movie Programs, 1981 (Box 68)
      - Nation of Nations Exhibition, A, undated (Box 68)
      - National Public Radio: A World of Difference, 1979 (Box 68)
      - Personal Communiqué State Edition, 1978 (Box 68)
      - Pi Delta Epsilon Handbook, 1956 (Box 68)
      - Political Humor Conference, 1975 (Box 68)
      - Popular Culture Association, The, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Quayle Quarterly, The, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Randolph Macon Woman's College Forum, undated (Box 68)
      - Reader's Report, undated (Box 68)
      - Realist, The, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Research Report: Russian Scholarship, 1979, 1980, 1982 (Box 68)
      - Richmond Wine Society, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Ringling Bros. & Barnum Bailey Circus, 1974 (Box 68)
      - Roll Call, 1977 (Box 68)
      - Sir John Soane's Museum - Hogarth Rake's Progress Slides, undated (Box 68)
      - Soviet Cinema Today, 1982 (Box 68)
      - Up in Michigan: First National Conference of the Hemingway Society, 1983 (Box 68)
      - Vanderbilt University, 1973 (Box 68)
      - Vanderbilt Planning Study, The, 1964 (Box 68)
      - VCU Magazine, 1975 (Box 68)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University Heritage University Course Offering, 1980 (Box 68)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University Popular Culture Conference, 1978 (Box 68)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, undated, 1970, 1996 (Box 68)
      - WEET Radio Jamboree, undated (Box 68)
      - WSFA Disclave, 1976 (Box 68)
      - York University Graduate Program in English: Modern American Literature: Southern Writing in Its Cultural Context, undated (Box 68)
      - Your Review: How to Print It the Easy Way, undated (Box 68)
      - American Literature, 1959, 1982 (Box 69)
      - American Historical Review, 1981-1982 (Box 69)
      - American Literary Scholarship, 1985 (Box 69)
      - American Studies Association, 1980-1982 (Box 69)
      - American Studies International, 1978, 1980, 1982 (Box 69)
      - American Studies International Newsletter, 1983 (Box 69)
      - Appalachian Journals, 1974 (Box 69)
      - Archives of Appalachia Newsletter, 1981 (Box 69)
      - Arlington Quarterly, The, 1969 (Box 69)
      - Association for Folklorist in the South Newsletter, 1981 (Box 69)
      - Blueprints: Newsletter of the National Building Museum, 1981 (Box 69)
      - CEA (College English Association) Critic, The, 1968 (Box 69)
      - Center for Southern Folklore, 1979 (Box 69)
      - Children's Literature Association Quarterly, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
      - Chronicle's Literary Issue of Sorts, 1982 (Box 69)
      - Discipliana, 1966 (Box 69)
      - Dispatch, The, 1984 (Box 69)
      - Extracts: an Occasional Newsletter, 1977 (Box 69)
      - Faulkner Newsletter & Yoknapatawpha Review, 1980-1984 (Box 69)
      - Glimpses: Elmira College & Mark Twain, undated, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Hemingway Newsletter, 1981, 1983, 1984 (Box 69)
      - Hemingway Review, The, 1983 (Box 69)
      - Honors College Essays, 1969 (Box 69)
      - Humanities in the South, 1981, 1983 (Box 69)
      - Iron Mountain Review, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Jessie Stuart Foundation Newsletter, The, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Journal of Modern, 1979 (Box 69)
      - Kentucky Review, The, 1981 (Box 69)
      - Markham Review, 1978 (Box 69)
      - Mark Twain Circular, 1987, 1988, 1991, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Mark Twain Journal, 1985-1986 (Box 69)
      - Melville Society Extracts, 1980, 1983, 1986, 1987, 1991 (Box 69)
      - MELUS News Notes, 1980, 1981, 1983 (Box 69)
      - Midwestern Miscellany, 1981 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous Journals & Newsletters, 1984 (Box 69)
      - Mississippi Quarterly, The, 1979 (Box 69)
      - MLA Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
      - More Books: the Bulletin of the Boston Public Library, 1944-1946 (Box 69)
      - Multi-Ethnic Literature of the United States, 1983 (Box 69)
      - Nathaniel Hawthorne Review, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Newsletter of the Association for Study of American Indian Literature, 1977 (Box 69)
      - Newsletter of the Society for the Study of Southern Literature, 1980-1983, 1990, 1992 (Box 69)
      - Newspaper and Gazette Report, 1978 (Box 69)
      - Notes on Contemporary Literature, 1978 (Box 69)
      - Poe Studies Association (PSA), 1979 (Box 69)
      - PTA Magazine, 1966 (Box 69)
      - RE: Artes Liberales, 1979 (Box 69)
      - Society for the Study of Midwestern Literature, 1980-1981 (Box 69)